TIN STIMAC

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Accomplished full stack developer with strong experience in the development of web applications like SaaS, CRM, eCommerce, market places, FinTech platforms, etc based on JavaScript and PHP. Have solid idea & knowledge of software development methodologies while being a proficient DevOps engineer who is familiar with the implementation of CI/CD based on Github/BB pipelines, Jenkins, Docker, etc.

EDUCATION

Zagreb University of Applied Science

Bachelor of Science BS - Computer Science 2008 - 2013

CONTACT

- ★ tin.stimac57@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/tin-stimac
- **2** Zagreb, Croatia

LANGUAGES

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- GraphQL
- PHP

BACK-END

- Node.js
- Express.js
- Nest.js
- Laravel
- Loopback.io,
- Symfony
- Codelgniter

FRONT-END

- React
- Angular
- Vue
- VueNext.js
- Gatsby
- Vuetify
- Nuxt.js
- Tailwind CSS
- iQuery
- SCSS

OTHER

- Agile-Scrum/Kanban
- AWS
- GCP
- Docker
- Kubernetes
- CI/CD

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Self-Employed | Full-Time July 2020 - PRESENT Zagreb, Croatia

- Developed front-end part of a case management platform using Angular
- Implemented a large front-end SaaS application using Angular according to wireframes as well as a back-end in Nest.js/Node.js
- Set up the AWS environment (AWS S3, AWS CloudFront, and AWS EC2)
- Designed database architecture and API based on GraphQL, PostgreSQL, NestJS
- Integrated a real-time dashboard for trading information using WebSocket

Technologies: TypeScript, Angular, React, GraphQL, Node.js, Material-UI, API, TypeORM, Nest.js, AWS

TIN STIMAC

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ARS Futura | Full-Time May 2016 - June 2020 Zagreb, Croatia

- Implemented a responsive React website from scratch for a social media startup
- Built an eCommerce platform using Nuxt.js, VueX, Shopify, Contentful
- Constructed a REST and Socket API in Node.js (using the Express.js framework and Socket.IO library)
- Created front-end of an eCommerce site based on NextJS
- Built an eCommerce back-end using NestJS, integrated PostgreSQL and used TypeORM
- Developed an application managing authentication/subscriptions/monthly payments flow
- Developed an event management web application where the client is able to manage his events and all of the guests.

Technologies: React, Vue, Nuxt.js, Next.js, Express.js, NestJS, Shopify, Contentful, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, TypeORM

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Lloyds Digital | Full-Time December 2013 - April 2016 Labin, Croatia

- Implemented messages and files receiving logic using webhooks and events subscription
- Helped front-end developers with Vue.js apps and other JS + HTML + CSS tasks
- Implemented messages and files sending logic using platform API calls
- Implemented app analytics, designed a lot of complex database queries, and performed optimization and caching
- Implemented an asynchronous long-polling service for receiving chat events using React
- Made it multi-threaded using various concurrent and parallel programming techniques

Technologies: Laravel, PHP, MySQL, React, Vue.js, Node.js